This is a perfect rep scheme that you can use to finally bench press 315 and this is
something that's going to help your triceps and your pecs get stronger so that you can
finally smash that goal.
We're going to start off with using our trigger sets concepts, which is something that we
use to predict when that 315 bench is going to come.
So let's start off with seven reps.
We want to work to about 250 pounds.
For a set of five, our main goal here is that we want to hit 270 pounds.
For a set of three, ideally we would hit 290 pounds.
So we're going to go 7, 5, 3.
These are the goal sets.
On that back end, now we're going to go 5, 3, 2.
Ideally we're going to hit 275 to 280 pounds for a set of five.
For a set of three, let's try to hit 295 for a set of two, between 300 to 305.
The rep scheme is 7, 5, 3, 5, 3, 2.
These are the goals, so now you can figure out where you're currently at and try to fill
in those goals based off of the numbers that you see currently to bench press 315.
Comment peak down below if you need help with your bench press, we're going to get you a
stronger and more explosive.
Peace.
- This is a.